sparktherise.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy policy - Spark The Rise

We collect information about you when you visit our Spark the Rise (“STR”) site, use our services, or view our online advertisements. The information which we collect and store during normal use of the STR site is used to monitor use of the STR site and to help further development of our products and services. In general you can visit M&M’s STR website on the Internet without telling us who you are or providing data that personally identifies you. Such use does not result in any personally identifiable data being collected or stored. “We”/”M&M” refers to Mahindra & Mahindra Limited, including its subsidiaries and affiliates (also referred to as  “us”, or “our”) (M&M, its subsidiaries and affiliates shall be collectively referred to as “Mahindra Group affiliates”).

Protecting your privacy and ensuring that your personal data is held securely is very important to M&M. We want you to be confident that we are looking after your interests and that is why we have set out our information practices in this Privacy Statement.

We do not share your information with third parties, unless we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested and we have asked for and obtained your explicit consent. The foregoing notwithstanding, if (1) disclosure was required by law, rule or regulation or was in response to a valid order of a court or authorized agency of government or other legal process and/or; (2) When we find your action on the STR web site violates the M&M terms and condition or any of your usage guidelines for specific products or services.

This Privacy Statement will apply when you use our STR website to discover more information about M&M and its products. This Privacy Statement is applicable to data collected by M&M and other M&M companies worldwide for use by these companies.

Whilst any application, request or enquiry you make, may be passed or made available to M&M Group affiliates some of which will be based in countries that do not have data protection laws, all M&M Group affiliates are required to comply with an internal Privacy Policy which requires that steps are taken to protect your Personal Data and for it only to be used for the purpose(s) for which it was submitted.

By submitting your Personal Data through this STR website, you shall be consenting to it being processed in the manner described above by M&M Group affiliates around the world and our hosting organizations around the world.

If you have submitted Personal Data through this STR website and wish us to cease using it for the purposes submitted, please contact us.

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several [self regulatory frameworks](http://www.google.co.in/intl/en/policies/privacy/frameworks/). When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will ensure that your rights under this Privacy Policy are not reduced due to any change in our Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

If you click on a third-party link, including a social media graphic link on the M&M STR website, you will be taken to the third party's web site, and your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. Likewise, whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

M&M STR website content is also integrated into other web sites. These web sites may collect personal information from their visitors that may or may not be used in conjunction with the M&M STR website content. Prior to supplying any personal information to any third party company that links to the M&M website, please read and understand their privacy policy.

Advertisements are served by our STR website, advertising technology vendor appear on pages throughout the M&M STR website. Some advertisements may request personal information directly from you or take you to web sites that may request your personal information. M&M STR website has no control over these advertisers' privacy policies, so please examine the privacy policy of any company advertising on the M&M STR website prior to submitting any personal information in connection with the advertisement.

We have taken adequate measures to secure access to your personal data.

M&M regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Statement. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement or our treatment of Personal Data and information by completing our web contact form or by writing to us at the following addresses:

Mahindra & Mahindra Limited Gateway Building, Apollo Bunder, Mumbai - 400 001.India.

Mahindra & Mahindra Ltd., Mahindra Towers, Dr. G.M. Bhosale Marg, Worli, Mumbai - 400 018. India.

M&M may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
